diy-dating.com 2014-12-19

# DIY-Dating

|  |  Home   
---  
Create an Account   
Login   
Take the Tour   
My Partners   
Help   
| Main Help  
---  
Contact Us  
FAQs  
Marketing  
Tutorials  
Our Forums   
Contact Us   
About Us   
Jobs   
  
**_Forum Latest_**  
  
| 

Join for free | Login  
  
---  
  
Privacy Statement

| This Privacy Statement covers DIY-Dating's treatment of your personal information. This Statement does not apply to the practices of companies that DIY-Dating does not own or control, or to people we do not employ. 

DIY-Dating does not sell or rent your personally identifiable information (email address, IP address, or birth date). We do not collect your first and last name, street address or telephone number.   
  
---  
**Information Collection**  
In order to use this website, you must be an adult at least 18 years of age (or older if the lawful age in your state, nation, or locality, is higher than 18); When you register with DIY-Dating, you are required to provide contact information (email address), unique identifiers (username and password), and demographic information (birth date, gender, ethnicity, etc.). You also tell us something about your personal preferences and interests.   
**Information Use**  
We use information you submit to help you create a personal profile and to help connect you with members with attributes identified by you as being important. Your profile and optional photo are displayed on the site for public viewing and search by other site users.   
**Public Information**  
Public information you submit (such as gender, age, height, location, photo, etc.) is displayed in your profile and is meant to be viewed by the public. Photos and profiles must be approved by DIY-Dating to maintain the quality of the site. We monitor submissions to public areas by approving photos and profiles and reserve the right to monitor private areas if we suspect a violation of the Terms and Conditions. We reserve the right to remove, edit, delete or refuse any submission to a public or private area of the site.   
**Private Information**  
Private information (email address, IP address, birth date and time zone) is not displayed on the public areas of the site and is not available to other members. Email addresses are used to email account information and for internal marketing purposes. Birth dates are used to calculate age and zodiac sign. (Age and zodiac signs are displayed to other members)   
**Information Automatically Collected**  
DIY-Dating automatically receives and records information from your browser including your IP address, browser type and cookie information. Your IP address is a series of numbers which identify your computer. We use it to help maintain our site. It does not provide personally revealing information about you.   
**Cookies**  
Cookies are small files stored by your browser in your computer when you visit our site. We use cookies to improve our site and make it easier to use. Cookies permit us to recognize users and avoid repetitive requests for the same information when you change pages on the site. We use session cookies that are automatically deleted after each visit. Most browsers will accept cookies until you change browser settings to refuse them.   
**Security**  
DIY-Dating follows reasonable technical and management practices to protect the confidentiality of information stored on our system. Your account is password-protected for your privacy and security. If you have reason to believe that your account is no longer secure, you must promptly change your password. If you have worries about this - use the **Contact us** page to alert us of your problem.   
**User Submissions**  
Be aware that any personally identifiable information you choose to disclose on this site, in public on your profile or in private through email to other members, is done at your own risk and that it may be collected or used by others. Caution and good sense should always be used in disclosing your personal identity to others and in selecting the type of information that you post on the website or release to others. DIY-Dating is not responsible for the use of any personal information that you may choose to disclose while on or off the website.   
**Legal Disclaimer**  
DIY-Dating will disclose your personal information, without notice, if required to do so by law, if necessary to protect the personal safety of users or the public, to protect and defend the rights or property of DIY-Dating, or if we find that your actions on our website violate the DIY-Dating Terms and Conditions. We are not responsible for death, personal injury, pain and suffering, loss of work or any other loss suffered by your use of this site.   
**General**  
By using this site, you agree to this Statement and the Terms and Conditions. We may change this Statement by posting a new version on our site and a notice of the change. We encourage you to periodically review this Statement in order to be informed of how DIY-Dating is protecting your information. You agree to sign a non-electronic version of this document upon our request.   

* * *

| Definitions | Contact Us | Anti-Spam Policy | Privacy Statement | Terms and Conditions | Profile Terms and Conditions  
---|---|---|---|---|---
